<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Openshift on WebLogic Café</title>
    <link>http://weblogic.cafe/tags/openshift/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Openshift on WebLogic Café</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2018, Mark Nelson</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 08:30:16 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://weblogic.cafe/tags/openshift/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>WebLogic on OpenShift</title>
      <link>http://weblogic.cafe/posts/weblogic-on-openshift/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 08:30:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://weblogic.cafe/posts/weblogic-on-openshift/</guid>
      <description>In this post I am going to walk through setting up and using WebLogic on OpenShift, using the Oracle WebLogic Server Kubernetes Operator. My starting point is the OpenShift Container Platform server that I set up on OCI in this earlier post.
I am going to use the operator to manage my domains in OpenShift. The operator pattern is common in Kubernetes for managing complex software products that have special lifecycle requirements, different to the base assumptions made by Kubernetes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Relocate the /var/lib/docker storage on an OpenShift system</title>
      <link>http://weblogic.cafe/posts/openshift-relocate-var-lib-docker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 18:02:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://weblogic.cafe/posts/openshift-relocate-var-lib-docker/</guid>
      <description>Today I ran out of space in the filesystem containing the /var/lib/docker directory on my OpenShift system, which meant I could not schedule any new pods (you get an error about disk pressure). So I decided I needed some more space.
I created a new partition with parted and then I updated my /etc/fstab to include that partition, with it mounted at /var/lib/docker. Then I made a new XFS filesystem on the with this command:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Running OpenShift on OCI</title>
      <link>http://weblogic.cafe/posts/openshift/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://weblogic.cafe/posts/openshift/</guid>
      <description>In this post, I want to share my experiences with running OpenShift on Oracle Cloud Infrastructure (OCI). This is not strictly a &amp;ldquo;how to&amp;rdquo; because I did set this up as a test/development system, not a production one, so I did take a few small short cuts, but I hope that it is still helpful to share.
I am going to set up OpenShift Enterprise 3.11 on a single compute instance on Oracle Cloud Infrastructure (OCI), so I am using the &amp;ldquo;all in one&amp;rdquo; configuration.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>