<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>WebLogic Café</title>
    <link>http://weblogic.cafe/</link>
    <description>Recent content on WebLogic Café</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2018, Mark Nelson</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 10:00:29 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://weblogic.cafe/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Oracle Cloud Infrastructure provider for Spinnaker</title>
      <link>http://weblogic.cafe/posts/spinnaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 10:00:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://weblogic.cafe/posts/spinnaker/</guid>
      <description>Over the last year or so, we have had a group of developers working on the Oracle Cloud Infrastructure provider for Spinnaker. All of this code has gone directly into the Spinnaker repositories on GitHub and it is all open source.
We are now at the point where the provider is pretty much fully functional and we have published documentation on the spinnaker.io site, and Spinnaker have updated their site to list Oracle Cloud Infrastructure as one of the supported providers, so that is a nice milestone for us!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WebLogic Kubernetes Operator 2.0 Release Candidate now available</title>
      <link>http://weblogic.cafe/posts/wko2rc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2018 08:00:23 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://weblogic.cafe/posts/wko2rc/</guid>
      <description>We have just made our 2.0 Release Candidate 1 of the Oracle WebLogic Server Kubernetes Operator available for early adopters.
The 2.0 release adds some significant new features including:
 Support for burning your WebLogic domain into the Docker image, in addition to supporting the domain being on persistent storage, The operator is now installed using Helm charts, replacing the earlier scripts, You can override domain configuration using configuration override templates, Load balancers and Ingress can now be independently configured, WebLogic logs can be directed to a persistent volume or the WebLogic server console output (stdout) can be directed to the pod log, Added lifecycle support for servers and significantly more configurability for generated pods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Running OpenShift on OCI</title>
      <link>http://weblogic.cafe/posts/openshift/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://weblogic.cafe/posts/openshift/</guid>
      <description>In this post, I want to share my experiences with running OpenShift on Oracle Cloud Infrastructure (OCI). This is not strictly a &amp;ldquo;how to&amp;rdquo; because I did set this up as a test/development system, not a production one, so I did take a few small short cuts, but I hope that it is still helpful to share.
I am going to set up OpenShift Enterprise 3.11 on a single compute instance on Oracle Cloud Infrastructure (OCI), so I am using the &amp;ldquo;all in one&amp;rdquo; configuration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello</title>
      <link>http://weblogic.cafe/posts/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 10:02:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://weblogic.cafe/posts/hello/</guid>
      <description>Hello and welcome to my new blog!
I am an architect at Oracle, and I work in the WebLogic team. I work with technologies like Docker, Kubernetes, Istio, OpenShift, ELK, Prometheus, Grafana, as well as developer focused technology areas like CI/CD. So that&amp;rsquo;s the kind of thing I will be writing about here!
I hope you come back soon to read my first real post!
p.s. I am just getting started setting up the blog, I am using Hugo for this blog, unlike my old blog which used WordPress, so I am learning how to drive Hugo!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>